A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, William J. Ronan, Series 29 FA371
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reference Files, 1945-1971; 2; 17.4 Cubic Feet
  - New York State Activities/State Government - Eastern Regional Conference of the Council of State Governments, June 1964 (Box 35, Folder 406)
  - New York State Activities/State Government - "Members of State Courts of Last Resort and Their Terms of Office," A Compilation Prepared for the Conference of Chief Justices, July 1965 (Box 35, Folder 407)
  - Governors Conference - Proceedings of the Governors' Conference, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 408)
  - Governors Conference - Proceedings of the Governors' Conference, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 409)
  - Governors Conference - Proceedings of the Governors' Conference, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 410)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Periodic Congressional Reassessment of Federal Grants-in-Aid to State and Local Governments, June 1961 (Box 36, Folder 411)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - State Constitutional and Statutory Restrictions on Local Government Debt, September 1961 (Box 36, Folder 412)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Local Non-property Taxes and the Coordinating Role of the State, September 1961 (Box 36, Folder 413)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - State Constitutional and Statutory Restrictions Upon the Structure, Functional, and Personnel Powers of Local Government, October 1962 (Box 36, Folder 414)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Intergovernmental Responsibilities for Water Supply and Sewage Disposal in Metropolitan Areas, October 1962 (Box 36, Folder 415)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Measures of State and Local Fiscal Capacity and Tax Effort, October 1962 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Directory of Federal Statistics for Metropolitan Areas, October 1962 (Box 36, Folder 417)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - State Constitutional and Statutory Restrictions on Local Taxing Powers, October 1962 (Box 36, Folder 418)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Apportionment of State Legislatures, December 1962 (Box 36, Folder 419)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Transferability of Public Employee Retirement Credits Among Units of Government, March 1963 (Box 37, Folder 420)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - The Role of the States in Strengthening the Property Tax, Volume 1, June 1963 (Box 37, Folder 421)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Performance of Urban Functions: Local and Areawide, September 1963 (Box 37, Folder 422)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - The Role of Equalization in Federal Grants, January 1964 (Box 37, Folder 423)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations - Impact of Federal Urban Development Programs on Local Government Organization and Planning, May 1964 (Box 37, Folder 424)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - "The People Take the Lead," A Record of Progress in Civil Rights, 1954-1962, the Institute of Human Relations, January 1962 (Box 37, Folder 425)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - "The Journal of Educational Sociology," Special Issue, Puerto Ricans and Inter-American Understanding, May 1962 (Box 37, Folder 426)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - Voting, the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report (Box 37, Folder 427)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - Education, the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report (Box 37, Folder 428)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - Employment, the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - Housing, the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report (Box 38, Folder 430)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - Justice, the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - Civil Rights, Excerpts from the 1961 United States Commission on Civil Rights Report (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - "The 50 States Report," Submitted to the Commission on Civil Rights by the State Advisory Committees, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - "Equal Opportunity, Union Made," Published by the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - "A History of the New York State Library," by Cecil R. Roseberry, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Civil Rights - "Journal of Human Relations", Autumn and Winter, 1958-1959 (Box 39, Folder 436)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - The Children's Bureau and Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 437)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Sociological Theories and Their Implications for Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 438)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Selected, Annotated Readings on Group Services in the Treatment and Control of Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 439)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Delinquency Prevention, the Size of the Problem, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Identifying Potential Delinquents, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Family Courts, an Urgent Need, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Coordination on the National Effort for Dealing with Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Current Training Needs in the Field of Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - How Effective are Services for the Treatment of Delinquents?, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Comparison of Expenditures and Estimated Standard Costs for Selected Juvenile Delinquency Services, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 446)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Delinquency and the Adolescent Crisis, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 447)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - State Agencies and Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 448)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Community Programs and Projects for the Prevention of Juvenile Delinquency, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 449)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Staff and Training for Juvenile Law Enforcement in Urban Police Departments, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 450)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Survey of Probation Officers, 1959, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 451)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - A Survey of Sociological Instructors Who Teach Undergraduate Courses in Corrections, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 452)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Juvenile Delinquency - Prediction and Selection of Delinquents, "Juvenile Delinquency," US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 453)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 1 - Report of the Mental Health and Mental Retardation Sections of the State Planning Committee, July 1965 (Box 39, Folder 454)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 2 - Reports of Regional Committees, July 1965 (Box 39, Folder 455)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 3 - Reports of Regional Committees, July 1965 (Box 39, Folder 456)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 4 - Reports of Regional Retardation Committees, July 1965 (Box 39, Folder 457)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 5 - Reports of Task Forces on Mental Retardation, July 1965 (Box 39, Folder 458)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 6 - Reports of Task Forces on Mental Health, July 1965 (Box 40, Folder 459)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Mental Health - A Plan for a Comprehensive Mental Health and Mental Retardation Program for New York State, Volume 7 - Source Documents and Data: The Foundation for Planning, July 1965 (Box 40, Folder 460)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 1, The Licensing and Regulation of Retail Package Stores, January 1964 (Box 40, Folder 461)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 1, January 1964, copy 2 (Box 40, Folder 462)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 1, January 1964, copy 3 (Box 40, Folder 463)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 1, January 1964, copy 4 (Box 40, Folder 464)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 1, January 1964, copy 5 (Box 40, Folder 465)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 3, Mandatory Resale Price Maintenance, January 1964 (Box 40, Folder 466)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 3, January 1964, copy 2 (Box 40, Folder 467)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 3, January 1964, copy 3 (Box 40, Folder 468)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 3, January 1964, copy 4 (Box 40, Folder 469)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Moreland Commission - New York State Moreland Commission on the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law, Report and Recommendations No. 3, January 1964, copy 5 (Box 40, Folder 470)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "The Four Million," Report of the New York State Citizens' Committee of One Hundred for Children and Youth, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 471)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "Investment in Youth," New York State Youth Commission, 1955-1958 (Box 41, Folder 472)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "A Decade of Progress, 1950-1960," A Report on Services to Our Children and Youth, Presented by the Chairman of the New York State Committee for the 1960 White House Conference, Volume 1, March 1960 (Box 41, Folder 473)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "A Decade of Progress, 1950-1960," A Report on Services to Our Children and Youth, Presented by the Chairman of the New York State Committee for the 1960 White House Conference, Volume 2, March 1960 (Box 41, Folder 474)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "Summer Vigilance and Services for Youth," City of New York, Office of the Mayor, Commissioner of Youth Services, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 475)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "Reaching the Fighting Gang," New York City Youth Board, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 476)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Youth - "New York State Services for Youth Who Need Help," 1963 (Box 41, Folder 477)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Futures, State University of New York and Your Children (Box 41, Folder 478)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type A-1, Expandable Elementary School, 14-21 Classrooms, Report (Box 41, Folder 479)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type A-2, Expandable Elementary School, 21-28 Classrooms, One-Story, Report (Box 41, Folder 480)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type A-3, Expandable Elementary School, 21-28 Classrooms, Two-Story, Report (Box 41, Folder 481)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type B-1, Expandable Junior High School, 800-1000 Pupils, Report (Box 42, Folder 482)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type C-1, Expandable Senior High School, 800-1000 Pupils, Report (Box 42, Folder 483)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type C-2, Expandable Senior High School, 1000-12000 Pupils, Report (Box 42, Folder 484)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type D-1, Expandable Junior-Senior High School, 800-1000 Pupils, Report (Box 42, Folder 485)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type D-2, Expandable Junior-Senior High School, 1000-12000 Pupils, One-Story, Report (Box 42, Folder 486)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State of New York, Standard School Plan, Type D-3, Expandable Junior-Senior High School, 1000-12000 Pupils, Two-Story, Report (Box 42, Folder 487)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Educational Television, A Pattern for Progress in New York State, Published by the New York Telephone Company (Box 42, Folder 488)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Tomorrow's Challenges to the Medical Sciences," National Fund for Medical Education, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 489)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Master Plan for School District Reorganization in New York State," Report of the Joint Legislative Committee on the State Education System, 1947 (Box 42, Folder 490)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Research Foundation, Decennial Report, 1951-1961, State University of New York (Box 42, Folder 491)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "The Puerto Rican Study, 1953-1957," Sponsored by the Board of Education of the City of New York, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 492)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Capital Construction Report, The State University of New York (Box 43, Folder 493)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Trends in Financing Public Education, 1929-30 to 1959-60, US Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 494)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State University of New York, Summary Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 43, Folder 495)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State University of New York, Master Plan, Revised 1960 (Box 43, Folder 496)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Financial Report, 1960, Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 43, Folder 497)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State University of New York, Summary Bulletin, 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 498)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Accent on Higher Education," Report for 1960-1961, The University of the State of New York (Box 43, Folder 499)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "A Study of College and University Enrollments and Enrollment Trends in New York State," Cornell University Department of City and Regional Planning, Fall 1961 (Box 43, Folder 500)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Index to the Public Schools in New York State, Department of Audit and Control, October 1961 (Box 43, Folder 501)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Financial Report of the City University, 1961, Board of Higher Education of the City of New York (Box 44, Folder 502)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Report of the Commissioner's Committee on Reference and Research Library Resources to James E. Allen, Jr., Commissioner of Education, December 1961 (Box 44, Folder 503)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Education in the Sixties, How Much Will It Cost?" The University of the State of New York, December 1961 (Box 44, Folder 504)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Education of the Adult Migrant," US Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 505)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Interim Report, Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing, State of New York, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 506)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Vocational Education in the Next Decade, Proposals for Discussion, US Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, January 1961 (Box 44, Folder 507)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "The Time is Always Now, Education Cannot Wait, 1961-1963," Report of the Chairman, Board of Education of the City of New York, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 508)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Report to the Board of Regents of the University of the State of New York - State Department of Education on the Engineering Aspects of Establishing a Statewide Educational Television System for the State of New York, June 30, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 509)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Quality in Education in New York State, 1962, The University of the State of New York. (Box 44, Folder 510)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - A Long-Range Plan for the City University of New York, 1961-1975, Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 511)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - New Formula Proposal and Staff Studies, Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing, State of New York, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 512)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Final Report, Second Yellowstone Field Research Seminar, Atmospheric Sciences Research Center, State University of New York, Albany, May 1962 (Box 45, Folder 513)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - The Regents Major Legislative Proposals for 1963, The University of the State of New York, December 1962 (Box 45, Folder 514)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State University of New York, Summary Bulletin, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 515)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Interim Report, Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing, State of New York, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 516)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - Final Report, Joint Legislative Committee on School Financing, State of New York, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 517)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - School Quality Workbook, Handbook, The University of the State of New York, January 1963 (Box 45, Folder 518)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - School Quality Workbook, Handbook, The University of the State of New York, January 1963 (Box 45, Folder 519)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Building on Strength, New York's Plan for a Reference and Research Library Program," The University of the State of New York, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 520)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "A Comprehensive Plan for Comprehensive Care, Education for the Health Professionals: New York's Needs in an Age of Change," A Report to the Governor and the Board of Regents from the New York State Committee on Medical Education, June 1963 (Box 45, Folder 521)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Bricks Without Straw, A Look at the Multi-Trade Vocational High Schools in New York City," Women's City Club of New York, Inc., January 1963 (Box 45, Folder 522)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "The Search for Economy, Sharing Ideas and Practices for the Efficient Management of School Income and Expenditures," The University of the State of New York, 1963 (Box 45, Folder 523)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "A Critical Review of Research and Opinion on Phonics," The University of the State of New York, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 524)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Better Schools for a Million Children," Public Education Association (Box 46, Folder 525)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Intergroup Relations, A Resource Handbook for Elementary School Teachers, Grades 4, 5, and 6," The University of the State of New York, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 526)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - The Regents Major Legislative Proposals for 1964, The University of the State of New York, December 1963 (Box 46, Folder 527)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - State Aid to New York School Districts, 1963-1964, The University of the State of New York, December 1964 (Box 46, Folder 528)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "The Legislature and Higher Education in New York State," A Report by the Legislature's Consultant on Higher Education, Academy for Educational Development, December 1964 (Box 46, Folder 529)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - A Preliminary Legislative Report on the Rescheduling of the School Y ear, The University of the State of New York, February 1965 (Box 46, Folder 530)
  - Miscellaneous Publications - Education - "Studies of Public School Support, 1964 Series, Balancing Public School Needs With a Fiscal Support Program for 1965-1966," The University of the State of New York, January 1965 (Box 46, Folder 531)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 47)
- Arthur Levitt Clippings, 1959-1966; 3; 1 Cubic Feet
  Prior to 1966, clippings were accumulated on Democrat Arthur Levitt, who was New York State Comptroller from 1955 to 1979. More than 1,300 clippings were sorted, numbered, and placed into the following eight categories: Politics (including Levitt's proposals and views, as well as political views and editorials on Levitt), Local Government, Taxation, Financing, Legislature (mostly criticism and comment of the New York State Legislature by Levitt), Audit and Control, Education, and Miscellaneous. Clippings were further subdivided by year. Some of the clippings were also categorized as "significant," indicating the articles contained something damaging to Levitt, particularly a reversal or modification of a previously stated view.